http://www.lipsonneilson.com/privacy-policy

CARES Act Stimulus
Multijurisdictional Practice (MJP)
COVID-19 Resource Center Locations CloseLipson Neilson – Law Firm in Bloomfield Hills, Michigan
3910 Telegraph Road Suite 200 Bloomfield Hills, MI 48302
Phone: (248) 593-5000Fax: (248) 593-5040 More DetailsLipson Neilson – Law Firm in Las Vegas, Nevada
9900 Covington Cross Drive Suite 120 Las Vegas, NV 89144
Phone: (702) 382-1500Fax: (702) 382-1512 More DetailsLipson Neilson – Law Firm in Phoenix, Arizona
5343 N. 16th Street Suite 140 Phoenix, AZ 85016
Phone: (602) 626-8888Fax: (602) 626-5588 More DetailsLipson Neilson – Law Office in Reno, Nevada
1 E. Liberty Street Suite 600 Reno, NV 89501
Phone: (775) 420-1197Fax: (702) 382-1512 More DetailsLipson Neilson – Law Office in Colorado Springs, Colorado
102 S. Tejon Street Suite 1100 Colorado Springs, CO 80903
Phone: (720) 601-8008Fax: (702) 382-1512 More Details CloseSearch Search Full Site Search
Or Search By:
Attorney
Practice
Location Attorney: Attorney
Practice Areas: Practice Areas
Select Practice AreaAppellate LawBusiness & Commercial LitigationEmployment LawEstate PlanningHomeowner AssociationProbate LitigationReal Estate Law & LitigationDomestic & Family LawBusiness & Tax LawArbitrationEmployment LitigationSecurities Law & Private EquityElection LawProfessional LiabilityProbate & Trust AdministrationDiscipline DefenseSurety & Fidelity LawCARES Act StimulusMultijurisdictional Practice (MJP)COVID-19 Resource Center
Locations: Location
Select LocationLipson Neilson - Law Firm in Bloomfield Hills, MichiganLipson Neilson - Law Firm in Las Vegas, NevadaLipson Neilson - Law Firm in Phoenix, ArizonaLipson Neilson - Law Office in Reno, NevadaLipson Neilson - Law Office in Colorado Springs, Colorado
Search Locations: Location
Select LocationLipson Neilson - Law Firm in Bloomfield Hills, MichiganLipson Neilson - Law Firm in Las Vegas, NevadaLipson Neilson - Law Firm in Phoenix, ArizonaLipson Neilson - Law Office in Reno, NevadaLipson Neilson - Law Office in Colorado Springs, Colorado
Practice Areas: Practice Areas
Select Practice AreaAppellate LawBusiness & Commercial LitigationEmployment LawEstate PlanningHomeowner AssociationProbate LitigationReal Estate Law & LitigationDomestic & Family LawBusiness & Tax LawArbitrationEmployment LitigationSecurities Law & Private EquityElection LawProfessional LiabilityProbate & Trust AdministrationDiscipline DefenseSurety & Fidelity LawCARES Act StimulusMultijurisdictional Practice (MJP)COVID-19 Resource Center
SearchHome / Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyLipson Neilson P.C. (the Firm) has a long-standing commitment to safeguarding the privacy of information entrusted to us. The privacy principles and procedures set forth below are intended to tell you how we collect, use, and distribute user information via our public website (www.lipsonneilson.com).Types and Uses of Personal InformationIf you use this website, personally identifiable information about you may be collected and processed by Firm employees. In general, we only collect such information (such as your name, phone number and e-mail address) when you knowingly provide it to us. Additionally, the Firm may automatically collect or process personally identifiable information (such as your internet domain or IP address) as part of the operation of this website or during your activities on or use of this website. By using this website, you unambiguously consent to our collection, processing, transfer or use of this personal information. If you do not consent to any collection, processing, transfer or use of such information, please discontinue use of this website. If you believe the Firm is in possession of your personal data and wish to have it purged from our systems, please contact the Firm using the Contact form provided on this website.Sharing with Other Firm AffiliatesThe Firm may share our data, including personally identifiable information, with our affiliates. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will follow privacy practices no less protective than our practices described in this document, to the extent allowed by applicable law.How Personal Information Is Shared with Third-PartiesWithout the user's consent, the Firm will not sell, trade, or disclose the user's personally identifiable information to third parties that want to market products to the user. However, the Firm may disclose information to third parties assisting us in carrying out a transaction or providing a service for you (e.g., packaging, sending and delivering information to you, clearing financial transactions, or performing statistical analyses of our services). Additionally, the Firm may disclose information when required by subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process, or in response to activities that are unlawful or a violation of the Firm 's rules for use of the website, or to protect and defend the rights or property of the Firm.The Firm occasionally uses certain outside companies to help us deliver online communications. These outside companies may collect and use information about customers for marketing purposes, but this information is aggregated and thus not identifiable to a specific user.Security MeasuresThe Firm has implemented technological and operational security processes to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration or unintentional destruction. While no security measure can guarantee against compromise, the Firm regularly reviews and updates its security measures in an effort to provide appropriate security for all information held by the Firm.Modifications to StatementThe Firm reserves the right to change, modify, or update this statement at any time without notice. We indicate the date of the current statement below, so you know when it was last updated.Data Retention & Right to be ForgottenThe Firm will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purpose it was collected. If you believe that the Firm is in possession of your personal data, but wish to have it removed from our systems, please contact the Firm using the Contact form provided on this website.ChildrenThe Firm takes children's privacy seriously. The Firm asks children under the age of 18 not to send any personally identifiable information through Firm websites without the consent of their parents or guardians. The Firm encourages all parents and guardians to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of personal information on the internet. The Firm will not knowingly collect, use, or disclose to third parties any personal information collected from children, and we are committed to complying with applicable laws and requirements, such as the United States' Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).Linked WebsitesWe provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these websites, we encourage you to review the privacy statement posted on these (and all) third party sites. The Firm is not responsible for the privacy statements or practices of sites and services controlled by other companies or organizations.Use of CookiesThe Firm may use "cookies" in connection with operation of this website. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored on your computer by the Firm website server. Cookies are used for record-keeping purposes—the stored information can be retrieved by the Firm website server when you return to the website. This allows the Firm to personalize or regulate the use of the site, and also permits the Firm to automate the access and data-entry functions of the site (e.g., login information), and to tailor the appearance or presentation of the site to your preferences or interests. In general, we do not use cookies to track the navigational habits of identified users without the user 's consent. If you visit our site to read or download content, much of the information we do collect is statistical only (e.g., the domain from which you access the internet, the date and time you access our site, and the internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site) and not personally identifiable. We use this information about the number of visitors and their use of the sites in aggregate form to make our sites more useful and attractive to you.The use of cookies is common in such activities, and they are used at most major websites. You may wish to adjust your Web browser to inform you whenever a cookie is to be used, or to reject all cookies automatically.Contact InformationClients should direct comments or questions regarding this statement to their Firm attorney; employees to the office administrator; all other inquiries should be directed to the Lipson Neilson PC law firm using the Contact form provided on this website. Updated: November 11, 2018We Look Forward To Connecting With YouName*Email Phone*MessageLipson Neilson P.C. publishes this website to convey general information and not for the purpose of providing legal advice. This Web site and its contents do not create an attorney-client or any other relationship between Lipson Neilson P.C. and any visitor to the Web site. Electronic mail (“e-mail”) sent to Lipson Neilson P.C. or any of its lawyers will not create an attorney-client relationship.*
I Agree. ** Checkbox RequiredEmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms.
Bloomfield Hills, MI(248) 593-5000 Las Vegas, NV(702) 382-1500 Phoenix, AZ(602) 626-8888 Reno, NV(775) 420-1197 Colorado Springs, CO(720) 601-8008 attorneysbarsdownloadln-logoln-logolocationpractice
